Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org
ALL [lN SPANISH]:
♪ The city's called Duke
The state's called New Mexico ♪
♪ Among the gangsters
The gringos'  fame is inflated ♪
♪ 'Cause of the new drug
They created ♪
♪ They say the color is blue
And the quality pure ♪
♪ This potent drug' s runnin'
Through the city ♪
♪ And no one could stop it
If they wanted to ♪
♪ The cartel's runnin' hot because
They weren't getting respect ♪
♪ Talkin'  'bout some "Heisenberg"
Who owns the market now ♪
♪ No one knows the man since
They' ve never seen his face ♪
♪ The cartel's 'bout respect
And they ain't forgiving ♪
♪ But that homey's dead
He just doesn't know it yet ♪
♪ Heisenberg's fame has got
Down to Michoacan ♪
♪ From way far away
They want to taste that meth ♪
♪ That blue stuff
Has crossed the border ♪
♪ Now New Mexico' s
Livin'  up to its name ♪
♪ Looks just like Mexico
In all the drugs it' s hiding ♪
♪ Except there's a gringo boss
And he's known as "Heisenberg" ♪
♪ The cartel's runnin' hot because
They weren't getting respect ♪
♪ Talkin'  'bout some "Heisenberg"
Who owns the market now ♪
♪ No one knows the man since
They' ve never seen his face ♪
♪ The fury of the cartel
Ain' t no one escaped it yet ♪
♪ But that homey's dead ♪
♪ He just doesn't know it yet ♪♪
[IN SPANlSH]
What the hell
are they thinking?
Sending us some loudmouth
who doesn't speak the language?
FEDERALE [IN SPANISH]:
Politics, man. Politics.
VANCO: Supposed to
be some hotshot hero.
I say it's a bunch of crap.
FEDERALE: Hero for
Albuquerque, maybe.
Maybe it don't take
much up there.
Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org